Erman Kemanci

Click here to see my portfolio website

SKILLS



SOFTWARE

- Wordpress
- Visual Studio Code
- Visual Studio 2017, 2019
- SQL Server Management Studio 2016
- Mongo DB
- Postman

LANGUAGES

- Turkish
- English



PERSONAL PROFILE

I am an experienced self-motivated junior web developer and I am studying hard to improve myself to achieve my ambitions. I have been teaching myself variety of technologies since November 2018 using different learning sources including online courses. I am always curious about new technologies and keen to learn more.

I am a mature team worker and adaptable to all challenging situations. I am able to work well both in a team environment as well as using own initiative. I am able to work well under pressure and adhere to strict deadlines

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior Web Developer - Part Time The Developer Academy | June 2022 - January 2023

... - June 2022 - January 2023

- Worked on developing and maintaining several web applications using HTML5, CSS3, javascript, React. Node.js. and MongoDB as the backend database.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to ensure timely delivery of projects.
- Assisted in troubleshooting and debugging code issues

Freelance Software Automation Tester - Part Time <u>Flippler GmbH | February 2021 - August 2021</u>

• I worked as an automation tester, using Swagger, Postman, Azure platform, Space. I did not work with a UI to make tests so I was only responsible for endpoint tests on Swagger and Postman.

Website Creation and Maintenance Using Wordpress Sheffield | March 2020 - 2021

• I voluntarily made a website for Community Contact Tracers who have become well known nationally for their work during the pandemic.

IT Service Operations Analyst NHS Sheffield Teaching Hospitals | Feb 2019 - Feb 2020

- Making digital forms and dashboards for different departments by using Cherwell Business Management tool
- Following user accounts requests, restoring development environments using Cherwell, Commvault, SQL Server Management Studio 2016

PROJECTS

Beatmaker application with Javascript : This application lets the user create their own music with different sound effects.

- Please <u>click here</u> to see the Beatmaker app made with Javascript
- Please <u>click here</u> to see the Beatmaker app GitHub repository

To Do application with React: This application lets the user create a to do list, classify the actions and delete actions when completed.

- Please <u>click here</u> to see the To Do app made with react
- Please <u>click here</u> to see the To Do app GitHub repository

Wordpress Project : Please <u>click here</u> to see the Community Contact Tracers website

EDUCATION

• Bechelor Degree - Tourism And Hotel Management

<u>Abant Izzet Baysal University | Duzce, Turkey | September 2001 - Jun 2006</u>

Associate Degree - English as a Second Language

<u>Virginia International University | Fairfax, Virginia, USA | June 2008 - August 2008</u>

• Completed The Developer Academy Sector Routeways Digital Bootcamp

The Developer Academy | Sheffield, England | 2022

CERTIFICATIONS

- C# Fundamentals PluralSight | July 2021
- Complete HTML And CSS Web Dev. Essential Skills UDEMY | November 2020
- C# Intermediate : Classes, Interfaces and OOP UDEMY | June 2020
- Complete Asp.Net MVC Web Development UDEMY | April 2020
- C# Programming Online Microsoft Virtual Academy | January 2019
- SQL Fundamentals Online Microsoft Virtual Academy | January 2019
- C# Fundamentals for Beginners Online Microsoft Virtual Academy | December 2018

INTERESTS

Retro computers, console games, watching movies, cooking, running and weekly exercises.